Good night.
Good night. - Good night.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
MST rehearsal.
I'm off.
You might want to wipe that off so it doesn't slip.
The skirts on your costumes are too long.
I don't want you to be nervous.
I'm very nervous.
It's like paradise in heaven.
I put in the choreography right before the show.
I don't know how much I'm going to have to dance from here on out to make sure I don't get used to my body.
I'll start rehearsals tomorrow.
Rehearsals are going to start tomorrow.
See you there.
I'll be there.
Bye bye.
I'm so nervous!
I was about to cry during the first performance.
It hurts.
But I've only done it twice since the first time.
That's what I'm talking about! Suddenly you were working hard.
I worked so hard.
I have to dance about 100 times before I can sleep.
And, you know, Mr. Emstee says you can choose your meal!
Wow.
Ratatouille.
Cheese grilled!
Delicious.
Salmon Ratatouille
Cheese baked, delicious!
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you our menu!
Charcoal-grilled oyakodon
That looks delicious too!
Salmon Ratatouille with Cheese
Shrimp Chili Owa
Chicken with sweet & sour sauce
Sweet and sour
Complete Nutritional Food
Aged cold cooked chicken & enzyme brown rice
Ehhhh...
This is...
This is for you.
I'll have him do tomorrow's lunch.
Oh no, I'll choose.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm probably just going to go with what you said earlier... about how fresh you are.
Oh, you mean you're picking today?
I think you're probably right.
Oh, I...
Oh, wait, today's.
What?
Ha-ha-ha. - I'm still getting lunch.
I'll have lunch now, too. I'll have lunch. I'll have it for dinner.
Today's meal. From now on, today's meal.
Is it the same for everyone? No.
It's a complete meal. A complete meal.
Looks good.
That's done.
I've seen a lot of movies about a lot of different shows.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Hey, um, did you already have the blubbering shakes?
I did that guy thing a few times throughout the whole thing, but blubbering all the way through.
It's true, you know, the show, you sing with all the players in front of you.
In the beginning, they were right in front of me,
I sang like I was facing them.
You are being watched.
It was a different kind of tension from being watched.
It was amazing, just the realization that I was going to be wired,
When I was about to cry, the music station was on the screen behind me, so I had a colorful realization.
It was amazing.
I wonder if I'll be able to sleep much?
I sleep a lot.
It's totally whimsical.
I saw the announcement of the couples' weights, and I don't know what it was, but it was different from the usual,
It's a little bit different,
Everyone wanted a comella.
Everyone sang, Kitami-san.
The length of the tame (pause) and so on,
Oh! Kitami said, "Go home.
It's so big.
It's like they know what's going on,
Like you know what's going on.
Yes, that's right. He said, "Yay.
I naturally cried tears of joy,
I was really happy,
I didn't feel like a rapporteur or anything like that,
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm really happy.
I've been thinking about it for a long time,
I thought I wanted to see it as a guest, but I didn't get a chance.
I thought I wanted to see you as a client,
I thought I'd see you as a guest, but my hair was falling down,
I was thinking, "I won't be back,
I'm really looking forward to seeing you this year,
I was pretty much hooked after I came in,
I've been crazy about it since I came in.
I didn't think it would come true,
I am very happy.
I've been really into it since I was a little kid,
I've been watching the show ever since I was a little kid,
I've been watching the show ever since I was a little kid.
I've spent decades wondering if I'm even going to be on the show.
I don't think so.
I've never thought about it.
If I thought about it, I would be even more nervous.
That's right.
Don't remember.
It's strange, but I hope you're looking forward to it.
Yes, if you're looking forward to it. If you look forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best!
I look forward to working with you all.
Like I can find a lot of these things.
Like a table.
Yeah. - Yeah.
There's that set.
There's that set you see on TV.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
You know...
The theme song...
Or a message or something.
Oh, it's like M.
Oh, my gosh, I'm so excited I can't even keep track of it.
It's been a while since I've heard great music.
And everyone was so warm,
They were getting us excited, too.
I saw their eyes, too, and they were smiling,
They fell in love with me.
I fell in love with them, thanks to them.
When you appealed to me,
What?
Wow!
Surprised?
Yes, I was.
I cried so hard.
I didn't drink much water at that time,
I didn't think people could cry like that,
I cried so much.
There was so much aftertaste,
Extension!
Oh yeah!
I was like, "Will I be able to see my extensions the next morning? I'm like...
They look great on me, but they don't look great on me.
So I was really looking forward to announcing them to everyone!
We were waiting so long to make the announcement.
Two minutes to go.
It was so fast, this period of time...
One more week.
It went by so fast.
Everyone reacted so well to the fact that we were going to perform.
It really seems like everyone is very patient.
I'm nervous about tomorrow, but I'm going to practice a lot and try my best to have fun.
Please watch.
I'm going to sleep. I see.
Nice to meet you.
It's me, Akkai-bama.
It was Akcaibama.
It was Akkai-bama.
Bye-bye!
Thank you for your hard work.
I got a lunch from a delicious restaurant.
I hope to go home in good spirits.
I will do my best again tomorrow.
Bye bye!
The day I only ate kiwi, dried sweet potato and Chinese cabbage soup
Today I still have yogurt to eat
Second meal
If I eat after I get home, I'll gain weight, so I'll eat now and go home
I won't eat and go home
Thank you for your hard work
Go to bed early for tomorrow
I want to make sure I can't do it too soon
Good night.
See you tomorrow. Good night.
Otherwise, I can't walk.
Come on, let's go wherever you want.
Goodbye, goodbye.
After the rain, the streets were sparkling.
My heart is like a sunny day.
I play the rainbow piano
I don't know why, but when I smile, it's like the world is shining
It's like the world is shining
I turn my umbrella around and take it easy
I can't walk if I don't
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying
And somewhere I'll get my body wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
Walking down the street
And you're looking at me
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
When it's raining and it's raining and it's raining
I'll try to make you laugh
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
It's as if my heart is in a sunny mood
Rainbow pools of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My eyes I'll give Premi a try
I'm already feeling beautiful
vortex
Even though it's just the two of us...
She who is on the verge of extinction
For example
if you perish, you will perish
goodbye goodbye
At last
Singing Purple
Crying peace of mind
Same excursion
C lawsuit
Death würde decided
Dirde
carga
веч inner
through sh 나오는
look it up
говоря
I Kaiba
my voice
d android
пока
Oh!
Bobo
provision
приз
there
li
don't
alliances
w
бы
Thank you for watching